

Charlie Rios Pujado

Date of birth: 12/03/1999

Nationality: Spanish

CONTACT

Barcelona

08038 Barcelona, Spain (Home)

charkrios@gmail.com



(+34) 608435442



http://Charlie.icu



linkedin.com/in/Charlie-rios



ABOUT ME

Multi-role profile in IT.

Programmer oriented to web development, from Full-Stack programming to Layout and Web positioning.
IT specialist/manager with experience in systems/server administration oriented to

B2B (Business to business) services

Committed, proactive and constantly learning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

12/2022 - 04/2024 Ibiza (remote), Spain

Web Developer (Junior) Full-Stack Pixelimperium / Freelance

Web Developer

- Front-end and Full-stack
- Web layout with WordPress, PrestaShop and Shopify
- Development with React|S, Angular|S, MongoDB, SQL, Javascript, CSS, HTML, PHP, Git, NodeJS, REST
- Blockchain & Web3 Technology

05/2022 - 09/2022 Molins De Rei, Spain

IT Tech Lead & consultant DR Finantrust, S.L.

Finance-oriented business (broker)

- Manager in charge of IT department and teams
 - System Admin L4 role
 - Adviser in B2B IT
 - internal IT consultant

05/2020 - 05/2022 Hospitalet de Llobregat, Spain

Head of IT Businessprinter, S.L.

IT services company B2B (BusinessToBusiness)

- System Admin L3 role
- Head of the internal IT department (medium size company)
- Responsible of the field IT technicians team (5 people)
- Systems, servers & Networks administrator
- IT advisor B2B oriented

05/2017 - 05/2020 Cornellà, Spain

System Admin (L2) MagnumObject, S.L.

IT services & component distribution company

- Configuration and installation of (new) software/hardwareequipment
- Remote &/or in-person end-user assistance
- Resolution of hardware/software incidents
- Setup, management & maintenance of: VPNs, Servers, Networks, BackupSystems
- Resolution of incidents within office packages
- Windows / Linux (Ubuntu, Debian) / MacOS / iOS / Android
- Use of monitoring & visualization tools
- Stock control, RMA management and SAP department
- Management and monitoring of incidents with suppliers/manufacturers
- Web management
- Some B2B commercial tasks

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09/2019 - 06/2020 Barcelona, Spain

FP Grado Superior DAW (Web Apps Development) IOC (Institut Obert de Catalunya)

09/2017 - 06/2019 Barcelona, Spain

FP Grado Superior DAM (Multiplatform Apps Development) Salesians de Sarrià

09/2015 - 06/2017 Barcelona, Spain

Baccalaureate in Science/Technology Institut Proa (Proa's Senior Highschool)

09/2011 - 06/2015 Barcelona, Spain

E.S.O. (Highschool Diploma) Escola Solc

04/2024 – 06/2024 Helsinki, Finland

Fullstack Open Developer University of Helsinki

Website https://www.helsinki.fi/en

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Spanish | Catalan | English

OTHER LANGUAGE(S): Japanese | French